Pay attention to what Marta Riesco has said
atentos a lo que ha contado Marta riesco
on her Instagram account about Alexa
en su cuenta de Instagram sobre Alexa
Rivas. I found out about everything that
Rivas yo me enteré de todo lo que tuvo
Alexia had to do because the year she
que hacer Alexia porque el año que
reported she was out of work for a whole year, they
denunció estuvo un año entero sin
had to meet and in the end
trabajar tuvo que reunirse y al final
say, hey, I'll do what you want, but
decir Oye yo hago lo que queráis pero
please, I have to work. In the end, she
por favor yo tengo que currar al final
removed everything, I mean, referring to the
quitó todo o sea refiriendose a las
lawsuits, she didn't remove everything, it was for
demandas no quitó todo fue a
survivors and they put her to work on
supervivientes y la metieron a currar en
all the programs. That was the agreement that was
todos los programas Ese fue el acuerdo
reached. I also tell you that if I
al que llegó también os digo que si yo
had known everything that was going to happen to me
llego a saber todo lo que me iba a pasar
after my dismissal, my breakup, I tell you
después de mi despido mi ruptura os digo
that it would have been better for me to take the
que más me hubiese valido el
helicopter and throw myself into the sea. Yes, we
helicóptero y haberme tirado al mar sí
told you Marta, watch out, I
te lo dijimos Marta ojo que a mí Alexia
hate Alexia, she's one of those people I
me cae fatal es de las personas que
can say is terrible, but now I'm in the
puedo decir fatal pero ahora estoy en la
situation that she was in. I understand that she would
situación que ella estuvo entiendo que
sign and say, I'll do whatever is
firmara y dijera hago lo que sea
necessary, but I want to go back to
necesario pero yo quiero volver a
work. I completely agree.
trabajar Completamente de acuerdo